Some secrets are better left buried.
Don McKay is a crime, mystery, thriller film directed by Jake Goldberger.
Everything appears off-kilter when a man returns to his
hometown after 25 years to visit his former lover.
Don McKay, played by Thomas Haden Church.
Sonny, played by Elisabeth Shue.
Marie, played by Melissa Leo.
Samuel, played by M. Emmet Walsh.
Otis Kent, played by Keith David.
Dr. Lance Pryce, played by James Rebhorn.
Don McKay is a 2009 independent drama thriller film written and directed by Jake
Goldberger and starring Thomas Haden Church and Elisabeth Shue.
It premiered at the 8th Annual Tribeca Film Festival in April 2009
and received a limited release on April 2, 2010.
The tone is intense and mind_bending.